getyourfixtures.com 2016-11-22

# GetYourFixtures United States - Sports on TV - Football on TV - Soccer on TV - Streams and more - Wiziwig

**Getyourfixtures** makes every effort to ensure your online privacy. The processing of personal data on this website is fully in accordance with the provisions of the national legislation for the processing of personal data, as set out in this privacy statement.

This website/portal is the property of, and is administered by:

 **Zeegids BV / Contact us by E-mail:  ** **getyourfixtures[at]gmail.com**

In this statement the following terms are defined as stated below:

 **"** Name **":  ** **Getyourfixtures** **  
**"Service": the online platform and other online services offered by   **Getyourfixtures**  through its website  **Getyourfixtures.com** **  
**"User": the user of   **Getyourfixtures** ' online platform

 **Information collected**

 **Getyourfixtures**  collects information in a number of ways. Whenever you request information or order goods and services from us, we ask for your name, e-mail address and other relevant contact information. We only use the collected information to contact you for conventional user relations purposes and to facilitate the optimum use of our service.

 **Cookies**  
We use cookies and log files that allow us to collect important information about the use of the service. A cookie is a small data file that a web server sends to your browser, which then saves this file on your computer's hard disk. We use the information collected from the cookie to analyse use patterns and users characteristics, for system administration, to compile statistics on visitor activity and preferences and to produce reporting used for internal statistics that we use to improve our online services. Cookies are stored on your PC until you delete them. If you do not accept our use of cookies, you can set your browser to reject them. These details are not connected to any personal information and cannot lead to establishing your identity.

 **Opt-in**  
Our website's features are "opt-in," meaning that users can decide whether to subscribe to our newsletters, special offers and other information on new opportunities, events and services. You will not receive e-mail marketing offers from us until you give us your permission to send them to you. If at any time you no longer wish to receive information in a particular area and wish to be deleted from a mailing list, send an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/web/20161122165749id_/http%3A//www.getyourfixtures.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) /* */ with the subject line "unsubscribe."

 **Information to third parties**  
Your information will never be provided to any external parties unless you explicitly give permission for us to provide it or unless we are obliged by law to do so.

 **Changes**  
You may at any time review and change the personal information you have provided. You have the right to block the processing of the information for the purposes described above. Opting to have a user's information blocked from processing will not be subject to any fee. To block the processing of your information, you must contact  **Getyourfixtures**  using the contact information (e-mail, telephone number or fax) listed above.

 **Security**  
We make every effort to provide an adequate level of protection possible with regard to your personal details and to prevent any unlawful use of them.. This Service/website is equipped with features to protect the information we receive from you against loss, abuse and modification. Only authorized personnel have access to your details. The saving and passing along of your details via the Internet are protected by current standard methods.

 **IP Addresses/Cookies**  
Getyourfixtures' web server automatically collects so-called 'IP Addresses'. Your IP Address is a number by which other computers on the network can identify your computer, so that data (such as internet pages) can be sent to your computer. You cannot be personally identified with an IP Address.

A cookie is a compact piece of information that is saved onto your computer. During a visit to the Getyourfixtures website this cookie is turned on and consulted. We use IP Addresses and cookies to analyse trends, to manage this website, to follow the use of the site (for example, the number of visitors to the site, busy and quiet periods).

Perhaps unnecessarily, these details are not connected to any personal information and cannot lead to establishing your identity. 

 **Links**  
This Getyourfixtures website contains links to other websites and/or sources. Getyourfixtures bears no responsibility or liability for any of these. We advise you to always read the privacy statements of other sites/sources carefully before you provide them with any of your personal details.

 **Protection of information**  
Getyourfixtures makes every effort to provide the highest level of protection possible with regard to your personal details and to prevent any unlawful use of them. Only authorized personnel have access to your details. The saving and passing along of your details via the Internet are protected by current standard methods.

 **Changes**  
This privacy statement is restricted to the use of, and possibilities on, this website. Any future changes or updates to this site could lead to changes in this privacy statement. It is therefore recommended to check this privacy statement regularly.

Finally, we shall use all information gathered via this site in accordance with this privacy statement and with the purpose for which the information was collected. If Getyourfixtures decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner that deviates from that specified in the privacy statement, Getyourfixtures will then inform the affected users of the site via email. The user shall then have the choice not to give his/her agreement for the information to be used in this manner.

 **Contact**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the functioning of the Service or our treatment of you as user, please contact us by e-mail using the contact information provided above.
